tie.org 2015-06-07

# TiE Privacy Policy - TiE Global

#### **Overview**

Privacy is of great concern to most users of the Internet, and is a critical part of an enjoyable and satisfactory user experience. We are aware of, and sensitive to the privacy concerns of our subscribers and other visitors to our Website. Whether you are a customer of our various products and services, or a visitor to our site, we assure you that we do not collect personal information from you unless you provide it to us. Please note that our site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices, privacy statements, or content regarding these other sites.

#### **Anti Spam Policy**

We are committed to complying with the [U.S. CAN-SPAM Act of 2003](http://www.business.ftc.gov/documents/bus61-can-spam-act-compliance-guide-business) and the [European Union E-Privacy Directive](http://europa.eu/legislation_summaries/information_society/legislative_framework/l24120_en.htm) at all times.

#### **Cookies**

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows us to recognize you each time you visit this site (customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and we do not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds, Google Analytics, etc.

#### **Privacy Rights**

We are committed to protecting your privacy online. When you visit our site, we may collect personal information from you such as your name, e-mail address, home address, phone number, etc. Our third party hosting company will collect additional information such as the URL you came from, your IP address, your domain name, your browser type, the country and state where your server is located, and the pages that were viewed during your visit to our site. All this information is kept on a secure server to protect it from outside parties.

We do not sell or rent personal information to others. We use your information only for the limited purposes of sending you updates and useful information about our programs, promotional information, enhancing the site operation, for statistical purposes, and for overall systems administration.

#### **Our Security Procedures**

We consider the protection of all personal information we receive from our Web site visitors and subscribers as critical to our mission. Please be assured that we have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of any personal information we receive from you. As with any transmission over the Internet, however, there is always some element of risk involved in sending personal information. In order to try to minimize this risk, we encrypt all information that you submit in ordering one of our products or services using the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

We understand and respect the right to privacy.  
Please report any non-compliance or abuse to support@tie.org
